https://www.irishgirlguides.ie/privacy-policy/

Irish Girl Guides
Home Page
Login to Leader Area
Search for:
Our Privacy Policy
Irish Girl Guides is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the Irish Girl Guides Privacy Statement to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of the Irish Girl Guides website. The Irish Girl Guides website is owned and operated by Irish Girl Guides.
Irish Girl Guides reserves the right to change, modify or update this statement at any time without notice.
Voluntary Submission
Irish Girl Guides does not collect personally identifying information about any individual Irish Girl Guides web site user except when knowingly provided by such individual. For example, you might be asked for information when you register for using one of the site’s features or to receive a newsletter. You always have the option not to provide the information requested. If you choose not to provide the information requested, you can still visit most of the Irish Girl Guides web site, but you may be unable to access certain options and services.
Cookies
A cookie is a small data file that certain web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can’t read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Irish Girl Guides uses cookies solely to improve the visitor’s experience, for example, to keep track of the access rights assigned to a user, or to automatically fill-in repetitive forms with information previously provided. This could occur when posting a message on the discussion forums or submitting a profile.
Most web site browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser settings to display a warning before accepting a cookie, or to refuse all cookies. However, if you choose to disable the receipt of cookies from the Irish Girl Guides web site, you may not be able to use certain features of the site.
Browser Level Information
Irish Girl Guides web servers automatically collect information about a site user’s IP address, browser type and referrer by reading this information from the user’s browser (information provided by every user’s browser). This information is collected in a database and used – in an aggregated, anonymous manner – in the internal analysis of traffic patterns within the Irish Girl Guides web site. This information is automatically logged by most web sites.
Use of Information
Irish Girl Guides may disclose information about its users when believing in good faith that the disclosure is required by law.
Please be aware that Irish Girl Guides’ sponsors, advertisers or web sites that have links on the Irish Girl Guides web site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those parties and web sites linked to Irish Girl Guides are not covered by this privacy statement.
Irish Girl Guides web site users should also be aware that when you voluntarily disclose personal information on bulletin boards or forums, that information may be collected by others and may result in unsolicited messages from others.
The safety of children is very important to Irish Girl Guides. Whilst Irish Girl Guides will make every reasonable effort to ensure that children’s privacy and other rights are not compromised, it is ultimately the responsibility of parents to monitor their children’s Internet usage. Children should always ask a parent before sending any transmission over the Internet.
YOUR DATA SETTING
[wordpress_gdpr_privacy_settings]
Data Access Request
To request your user data report, click in the link below:
Request Report
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.
Read More
Accept
Decline
Cookie Settings
I consent to the use of following cookies:
Necessary
Marketing
Analytics
Preferences
Unclassified
Cookie Declaration
About Cookies
Necessary (5)
Marketing (4)
Analytics (10)
Preferences (0)
Unclassified (2)
Necessary cookies help make a website usable by enabling basic functions like page navigation and access to secure areas of the website. The website cannot function properly without these cookies.
Name
Domain
Purpose
Expiry
Type
wpl_user_preference
www.irishgirlguides.ie
WP GDPR Cookie Consent Preferences
1 year
HTTP
m
m.stripe.com
Determines the device used to access the website. This allows the website to be formatted accordingly.
2 years
---
__stripe_mid
www.irishgirlguides.ie
For processing payment and to aid in fraud detection.
1 year
HTTP
__stripe_sid
www.irishgirlguides.ie
Stripe Cookie to process payments
session
HTTP
YSC
youtube.com
YouTube session cookie.
Session
HTTP
Marketing cookies are used to track visitors across websites. The intention is to display ads that are relevant and engaging for the individual user and thereby more valuable for publishers and third party advertisers.
Name
Domain
Purpose
Expiry
Type
VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE
youtube.com
YouTube cookie.
Session
HTTP
GPS
youtube.com
Google advertising domain
Session
HTTP
test_cookie
doubleclick.net
A generic test cookie set by a wide range of web platforms.
Session
HTTP
_fbp
livestream.com
Facebook Pixel advertising first-party cookie
3 months
HTTP
Analytics cookies help website owners to understand how visitors interact with websites by collecting and reporting information anonymously.
Name
Domain
Purpose
Expiry
Type
_ga
irishgirlguides.ie
Google Universal Analytics long-time unique user tracking identifier.
2 years
HTTP
_gid
irishgirlguides.ie
Google Universal Analytics short-time unique user tracking identifier.
1 day
HTTP
_gat
irishgirlguides.ie
Google Analytics tracking cookie.
Session
HTTP
tk_ai
www.irishgirlguides.ie
JetPack analytical cookie that stores a randomly-generated anonymous ID. This is only used within the admin area and is used for general analytics tracking.
5 years
HTTP
IDE
doubleclick.net
Google advertising cookie used for user tracking and ad targeting purposes.
1 day
HTTP
vuid
livestream.com
Vimeo tracking cookie
2 years
HTTP
_gcl_au
livestream.com
Used by Google AdSense for experimenting with advertisement efficiency across websites using their services.
3 months
---
__utmz
livestream.com
Google Analytics campaign and traffic source tracking cookie.
6 months
HTTP
_gat_UA-39797287-1
livestream.com
This is a pattern type cookie set by Google Analytics, where the pattern element on the name contains the unique identity number of the account or website it relates to. It appears to be a variation of the _gat cookie which is used to limit the amount of data recorded by Google on high traffic volume websites.
Session
---
_gat_UA-1169997-20
livestream.com
This is a pattern type cookie set by Google Analytics, where the pattern element on the name contains the unique identity number of the account or website it relates to. It appears to be a variation of the _gat cookie which is used to limit the amount of data recorded by Google on high traffic volume websites.
Session
---
Preference cookies enable a website to remember information that changes the way the website behaves or looks, like your preferred language or the region that you are in.
We do not use cookies of this type.
Unclassified cookies are cookies that we are in the process of classifying, together with the providers of individual cookies.
Name
Domain
Purpose
Expiry
Type
mphb_session
www.irishgirlguides.ie
---
---
Cookies are small text files that can be used by websites to make a user's experience more efficient. The law states that we can store cookies on your device if they are strictly necessary for the operation of this site. For all other types of cookies we need your permission. This site uses different types of cookies. Some cookies are placed by third party services that appear on our pages.
Cookie Settings
×
Item Added to your Cart!
There are no products
Subtotal:
: €0.00
View Cart
Checkout
Continue Shopping
NOTICE:
IGG staff are currently work remotely. For general enquiries, telephone 016683898 or email info@irishgirlguides.ie.
The shop will be open Monday to Wednesday from 9am to 3pm from the 16/11/2020 till 04/01/2021. Web shop orders may be made via our online shop >> https://www.irishgirlguides.ie/shop/
Dismiss
